joblinker.net 2007-03-15

# Joblinker.net Privacy Policy

Effective **01/01/2002**

**Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**  
Our Commitment To Privacy   
The Information We Collect   
How We Use Information   
Our Commitment To Data Security   
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy   
How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Joblinker.net website from the server that hosts Joblinker.net. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Names  
Addresses  
Email addresses  
Phone numbers  
Resume information

We also partner with external websites that may provide online services and may choose to collect information.  Information collected by other websites promoted on the Joblinker.net website is subject to the privacy policy of such websites.

Personal  and contact information provided for the free resume evaluation offer is collected and distributed to Bakos Group and subject to their privacy policy found here:  [ http://www.bakosgroup.com/privacy.htm](http://www.bakosgroup.com/privacy.htm)

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send an email to  [web#Joblinker.net](mailto:web#Joblinker.net)

* * *

**Back to Resume Articles | Resume Examples | Resume Home**

* * *
